수키, 괜찮니?
물좀 줄까?
Sookie, are you okay?
You want some water?
4구라구요?
정말 시체가 4구였어요?
Four?
You're sure you found 4 bodies?
- 그런 정보를 알려줄 순 없다
- 제발 지금 저한테 그러지 마세요
- We shouldn't even be telling you this.
- Not now. Not with me.
- 관이 4개에 시체가 4구더구나
- 세상에
There's 4 sets of remains
inside four coffins.
- 거기 들어가면 안돼
- 당장 손 놓지 않으면 죽여버릴거에요!
Oh, my God.
We can't let you go in there.
If you don't take
your hands off me right now,
I swear to God, I will kill you.
안돼요, 안돼요
올라오지 말아요
Sweetheart,
you don't wanna come up here.
세상에 이게 뭐야
Jiminy Christmas.
- 뱀파이어들이 이렇게 된거에요?
- 보다시피
- That's what happens to vampires?
- Evidently.
아직 세 구나 더 남아있어
Plus, we got three more.
아침은 안먹고 온게 좋을껄
I hope you skipped breakfast.
버드가 신원 확인하라고 올려보냈든?
사실..
Did Bud send you up here
to make an ID? 'Cause...
수키 괜찮니?
Sookie, you okay?
눈누난나의 자막
2008.10.30 제작
수정금지/배포자유
눈누난나의 자막
피드백: lovnajing@naver.com
수정금지/배포자유
Synchro: mpm, Arrow
Episode 8 Season 1
True Blood S01E08
The Forth Man in the Fire
www.sub-way.fr / www.seriessub.com
- 빌 컴튼입니다
- 음성 메세지를 남기시려면 1번을..
- Bill Compton.
- To leave a voice message,
press one or just wait...
젠장!
Shit!
- 엄마, 아직 8시도 안됐어요
- 잘잤니? 나 때문에 깼어?
Mama, it's not even 8.
Good morning, baby.
Did I wake you?
거의 다 됐단다, 조금만 더 하면돼
I'm almost done.
Just a couple more loads.
- 아직 반이나 남았잖아요
- 필요 없는 것들이야
- These are half full.
- Useless to me.
악마한테나 필요했던거지
Just fuel for demon fire.
술 때문에 40년이나 악마가 있었어
술만 없으면 다신 찾아오지 않을거야
The bottle kept him alive
for 40 years.
As long as I keep the stuff out
of my house, he ain't never coming back.
- 얼마나 갈지 두고보죠
- 영원히야
- Let's see how long you can keep it up.
- Forever.
정말 영원히야
마지막 기회인걸
Gotta be.
I'm down to my last chance.
- 오늘 술 하나도 안마셨어요?
- 한 방울도 안마셨어
- You didn't have a drink today?
- Didn't need one. Didn't even want one.
- 이거 메이플시럽 냄새에요?
- 부엌에 가봐, 옥수수빵 만들어놨어
- Is that maple syrup?
- Check the kitchen. I made hoecakes.
정말이네요?
Are you serious?
- 옥수수빵 먹어본게..
- 할머니가 살아계셨을 때지
- I haven't had hoecakes since...
- Since your grandmama was alive.
엄마도 만들 수 있단다
그저 안만들었을 뿐이지
I always could make 'em,
just never did.
악마가 못하게 했었거든
The demon never let me.
- 베이컨 기름으로 구웠네요?
- 그렇게 먹어야 제맛이지
- You made these with bacon grease.
- It's the only way.
먹고 있으렴
You eat, baby girl.
난 저 악마놈 주스나 버려야겠다
I got me some more devil juice
to take out.
이럴수가
Goddamn.
당신..
You...
내가 만났던 사람들이랑 전혀 달라
You are not like anybody I ever met.
계속 그 말만 계속 하네
I was just gonna say the same thing.
오 주여
Jesus.
세상이 다 합쳐진 것만 같아
It felt like the whole world
came together.
나, 당신
Me, you,
이 침대, 우리 집
the bed, the house.
- 마치 하나의 커다란..
- 유기체같지
- We were all one big giant...
- Organism.
응, 정말 거대한 유기체
Yeah, mine was huge.
뱀파이어 피가 이렇게까지
할 수 있을진 몰랐네
I never knew vamp blood could do
something like this to you.
그거알아?
You know what?
나도 몰랐어
Neither did I. I mean...
전에도 같이 했던 파트너가 있었지만
이건 정말..
I've had V partners before,
but this was...
완전 다른 세상에 온 것 같아
on a totally different planet.
당신 정말 특별한 존재야
You're an extraordinary being.
- 그게 무슨 말이야?
- 어떻게 보면
- What's that supposed to mean?
- I mean, in some ways, we barely
우리 아예 모르는 사람들이긴해도
당신도 느꼈잖아
know each other, right?
But you felt that.
설마 나만 느낀건 아니겠지?
우리 서로 정말 친해진 느낌이야
Tell me that that wasn't just me.
We tapped into each other.
아냐 아냐, 나도 느꼈어
우리 친해졌어
No, I felt it. We tapped.
당신 내면 깊은 곳에 무언가
선하고 현명한게
There's something old
and good and wise
잠들어있어
난 알 수 있다고
deep down in you.
I have to know that person.
무슨 소리야, 말도 안돼
Come on, cut it out.
날 아는 사람 그 누구도
나보고 현명하다고 한 적 없어
Nobody who knows me
has ever called me wise.
그럼 아무도 당신을 모르는거야
Then nobody really knows you.
부끄러워하는거야?
Are you blushing?
당신 안떠났으면 좋겠어
I don't want you to go.
이것 저것 계획이 많긴 하지만
잠잘 곳만 구해준다면
I was planning on
just burning through,
but if you have a place
for me to crash
당신을 위해서
옆에 있어주지 뭐
then for you,
I might just stick around
- 잠시 동안만
- 있어줘
- for a little bit.
- Stay.
나랑 같이
Stay with me.
평생 침대 위에만 있고 싶다
I don't wanna ever leave this bed.
배고파질 때까지
여기 붙어서 V나 하자
Let's just screw
and do V until we starve.
좋아, 그럼 그냥
침대에 붙어있기만 하자
Sure. But, I mean,
let's hold off on the screwing.
나 좀 생각해줘
I'm a respectable girl.
뭐?
What?
내가 아프게했어?
Did I hurt you?
내가 너무 흥분했다면 미안해
그냥 정말 굉장했거든
I'm sorry if I got carried away,
it was just so amazing.
우리 섹스 안했어
We didn't have sex.
그럼 6시간동안 한건 섹스가 아니고 뭔데?
What do you call what we been doin'
for the past six hours?
V로 함께 했던거지
We were together on V,
그 누구와 함께였을 때보다 더 깊게 말이야
deeper than I've ever felt
with anybody ever before.
하지만 물리적으로는
우린 거의 손도 안댔어
But physically, we barely touched.
- 정말이야
- 말도 안돼
- I promise.
- That's not possible.
아직 팬티도 입고 있잖아
Panties still on.
- 그럼 이게 대체..
- 내가 말했잖아
- What... the fuck?
- I told you.
섹스보다 훨씬 낫다고
It's better than sex.
이런 세상에!
대체 뭐하고 있는거야?
Jesus Christ,
what the hell are you doing?
세상에는 무슨 세상에!
청소하는거 아니면 뭘로 보이는데?
Opith the J.C.
I'm cleanin', what does it look like?
- 조심히좀 걸어, 방금 청소했다고
- 계단 청소나 하지
- Watch your feet. I just waxed.
- I hope you mean the floor.
무슨 일로 온거야?
나 지금 청소하느라 바빠
- Can I help you?
- I'm up to my elbows in Easy-Off.
- 우리 엄마가 옥수수빵을 만들어준거 있지
- 근데?
- My mama made me hoecakes this morning.
- So?
아침을 만들어줬다고
She cooked me breakfast.
언제 우리엄마가 술 마실 때 빼고
오전에 손가락 하나 까딱하든?
When's the last time you saw
my mama lift a finger before noon
for anything besides Mad Dog 20/20?
어제 445달러짜리 후두교식 엑소시즘하러
무슨 숲에 갔었거든, 말도 하기 싫다
We went into the woods to get a $445
hoodoo exorcism last night.
You do not wanna get me started
우리 할머닌 돌아가셨어
- on that.
- My grandmother's dead.
적어도 넌 아침만들어줄 사람은 있잖아
At least you got someone
to make breakfast for you.
오지랖 넓게 참견하기 전에
그 사람 사정이 어떤지 생각도 안하지?
You ever stop thinkin' about
what's happening with others
- before you barge in on them?
- Sorry. I didn't me...
미안해, 난 그냥..
미치겠네, 그거 이빨자국이야?
Oh, my God, are those fang marks?
이게 뭐? 모두가 날 버렸을 때
누군가는 날 신경써줬다는 증표인데!
So what? It means someone cared for me
when everyone else left me high and dry.
미쳤구나 정말
뱀파이어가 피 빨아먹게 내버려두고!
No wonder you're crazy.
A vampire made a meal of you.
왜 다들 뱀파이어가 괴물이라고 생각해?
Why am I the only person that doesn't
think vampires are monsters?
우리 피를 먹고 살잖아!
They drink our blood.
What's to say Bill won't leave you
자기 욕심 채우고
떠나지 않을거란 보장 있어?
- once he's had his fill?
- Do you have any idea
너 오늘 나한테 무슨 일이
있었는지 알기나해?
what I've been through today?
- 친구라면 물어봐야지!
- 그런소리 하지도 마
- A friend would ask.
- Don't tell me how to be your friend.
- 네 친구는 나뿐이야, 오 하나님
- 함부로 하나님 운운하지마
- I'm the only one you got, goddamn...
- Lord's name in vain.
- 집어치워
- 당장 우리 집에서 나가!
- Fuck off.
- Get out of my house!
아주 너 덕에 너랑 절교하는건 시간문제야 지금!
I've gotten very good at losing people.
You are only making it easier for me.
못된년, 난 여기 오기도 싫었어!
그렇게 외톨이로 살고 싶으면 그러던가!
Bitch, I don't even wanna be here.
If you are hell-bent on being alone
in this world,
I ain't gonna stop you.
이럴수가
Oh, man.
나 정말 당신이랑 섹스하는거 별로야
진짜 상상도 못할껄
I wanna not have sex
with you again so bad,
you don't even know.
나한테 좋은 생각이 있어
I think I got some idea.
근데 어제 했던 V가
마지막이었어
But that V that we did
was the last I had.
- 그럼 어디가서 더 구하지?
- 필요하면 나가서 구하면되지
Where do we score some more?
When we need more,
we'll go out and get it.
욕심내기는
얼마 동안은 괜찮을꺼야
Don't be greedy.
We'll be okay for a while.
- 아침이나 먹어
- 정말 안먹을꺼야?
- Just eat your breakfast.
- You sure you don't want some?
- 페퍼로니랑 소세지 피잔데
- 난 유기농만 먹어
- Pepperoni and sausage.
- No, thank you. I only eat organic.
신체를 정화시키고
V를 더 잘 느끼게 해주지
The cleaner my body is,
the more intensely I feel the V.
근데 왜 텔레비젼이 두개야?
Why do you have two televisions
in the same room?
아래 있는건 안돼
부모님이 물려주신거라 갖고 있는거야
The bottom one's busted. I just keep it
'cause it was my parents'.
어떻게 돌아가셨는데?
Can I ask you how they died?
- 그 말은 별로 하고 싶지 않아
- 알았어
- I don't like to talk about it.
- Okay.
갑작스런 홍수 때문이야
It was a flash flood.
패리쉬 로드에 있는 다리에 갇혀 계셨었어
그러다 강으로 빨려 들어가셨지
They were caught on the bridge
down by the Parish Road
and got swept out in the river.
여동생이랑 난..
My little sister and I...
부모님이 나가계실 동안
할머니 댁에 있었어
were staying at our gran's
while they went out.
내가 수키를 잘 돌보지
못할거라 생각하셨거든
They didn't think I could
look after Sookie by myself,
거의 11살이었는데 말이야
even though I was almost 11.
가끔씩은 내가 더 나은 애였다면
하고 생각해
Sometimes I think,
if I was a better kid,
그럼 우리를 할머니네 집에
맡기러 갈 일은 없었을테니까
they wouldn't have had
to drop us off at Gran's.
그럼 부모님은 그 다리에 있을 일도 없었고
Then they wouldn't have been
on the bridge at the exact point
그 날..
when...
그럼 할머니 손에 자란거야?
So your grandma raised you
after that?
응 18살때 여기로 이사오기 전까진
Yeah, I moved back here
when I was 18,
여전히 할머니가 돌봐주시긴 했지만
even though Gran would have
rather kept an eye on me.
할머니도 돌아가셨어
Yeah, she passed too.
지난주에
Last week.
정말 유감이야
God, I'm so sorry.
젠장
Goddamn.
말할 생각 없었는데
이런말 절대 안하는데
I don't mean to be spillin'.
I never do this.
사람들하고 이런 말 안해?
여동생이랑도?
You never talk about things
with anybody?
You don't talk to your sister?
특히 여동생이랑은 안해
Least of all her.
걔랑만 있으면 난 정말 최악이야
할머니가 돌아가시고 크게 싸웠는데
She brings out the worst in me.
We had this big fight
after Gran died
내가 때렸지 뭐야
and I hit her.
정말 진심으로
I tell you,
난
I am
사상 최악의 오빠야
the worst brother in the world.
말도 안돼
That's ridiculous.
난 진정한 당신을 봤어
내가 직접 겪은 사람
I've seen who you are inside.
I've been there.
좋은 사람이야
And you're good.
알았지?
Do you hear me?
이쁘긴 하지
이거 사무실로 옮길까?
She's a beauty.
You want it for your office?
바에다 옮겨놓자
We'll put it over the bar.
술 취한 사람들은
얘네들하고 대화를 하더라고
Drunks like talking to the animals.
이것좀 봐
Check it out.
주머니쥐 거시기야
Possum prick.
- 어디서 났어?
- 지난주에 사냥한 놈이야
- Where'd you get that?
- Shot one last week.
비가 올 것 같아서
박제하려던걸 내버려 뒀지
It was gonna stuff it but I left it
back out. It got to raining,
3일이 지나 가보니
썩어서 뼈만 남았지 뭐야
then three days later, ain't nothing
left but possum sludge and bones.
이것만 건졌지 뭐
주머니 쥐 거시기는 이렇게 갈라져 있어
I saved this, though.
Possums have a two-pronged penis.
행운을 가져다 준다네
It's supposed to bring good luck.
그 이야긴 우리 둘만 알고 있자
Terry, let's keep
that story between us.
여자들은 오해할 수도 있잖아
The girls might get the wrong idea.
- 오늘 아침에 밖에서 뭐했어?
- 왜?
- What was you doing out this morning?
- Why?
홀딱 벗고 숲속을 뛰어 다닌다거나
그러진 않았지?
You wouldn't have been running through
the woods without no clothes on?
- 내가 왜 그런 짓을 해?
- 모르지
- Why would I do that?
- I don't know.
그래서 물어보잖아
That's why I'm asking.
낚시하러 갔다가 정말 맹세코 자네가
홀딱 벗고 나무사이를 뛰어다니는걸 봤어
I was out fishin'
and I could have swore
I saw you blazing buck-naked
through the trees.
난 아니야
It wasn't me.
자동차 수리했거든
I was working on my car.
근데 정말 똑같더라니까
It looked an awful lot like you.
알몸이었던걸 빼면
Except you wear clothes.
모르지 뭐
I don't know.
또 헛것이 보이는지도
Maybe I'm seein' things again.
보통은 죽은 사람이 보이는데
그러니까..
Except usually when I see people
who ain't there, it's...
- 반란군들 말이군
- 응
- It's the insurgents.
- Yeah.
- 오늘 본건 전혀 반란군 같지 않았거든
- 뛰어다녔다고 했지?
Only this fella I saw,
he didn't look like no insurgent.
But you said he was running,
though, huh?
나무도 엄청 많았을텐데
확실하진 않잖아
Plenty of cover in the trees.
How could you tell for sure?
자네가 본걸 봤다고 하는거겠지만
대체 누가 알몸으로 숲 속을 뛰어다니겠어
And I believe you saw what you saw.
I just don't know why anyone would
run naked through the woods
- 그것도 대낮에
- 그러게
- in broad daylight.
- Yeah.
자네 말이 맞겠지
Maybe you're right.
젠장
Shit.
이럴땐 정말 싫다니까
I hate bein' this way.
괜찮아
It's all right, buddy.
가자
Come on.
여기는 팔루자랑 멀어 괜찮아
We're a long way from Fallujah.
컴튼
사랑받는 남편이자 용감한 군인
COMPTON
BELOVED HUSBAND - BRAVE SOLDIER
목은 안돼요
Not the neck.
수키는 대체 어디간거야?
Where the hell is Sookie today?
음식 나왔어요
늦어서 죄송해요
Here you go, honey.
Sorry it took so long.
사람 많네
Intense.
벽에 있는 동물좀 봐
자연 박물관에 온 것 같아
All these animals on the wall,
it's like a natural history museum.
- 있는지 몰랐었는데
- 어떻게 모를 수가 있어?
- I never noticed them.
- How could you not?
여기 있는 동물들 전부 우리가
상상조차 할 수 없는 충만한 삶을 살았었을꺼야
Every one of these animals
lived a life full of experiences
that we can't even imagine.
너무 신경쓰이면
다른 데 가서 먹자
Does it weird you out?
We could go someplace else.
누구나 먹고는 살아야지
Everyone has to eat, right?
우린 우주의 먹이사슬 위에 있다고
We're all links
on the universal food chain.
봐, 다람쥐는 견과류를 먹고
See? Squirrel eats nuts,
뱀은 다람쥐를
악어는 뱀을 먹지
snake eats the squirrel,
gator eats the snake.
그리고 우린 원하는건
무엇이든 아무거나 먹고
And we can eat pretty much
anything we want.
다 돌고 도는거야
It's the circle of life.
오 세상에나
당신 마음을 핥고싶다
Jesus Christ.
I wanna lick your mind.
점심부터 먹자
Let's have lunch first.
주문 나왔어요
Order up.
죄송해요, 죄송해요
늦어서 죄송해요
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I know I'm late.
화재 사건은 나도 들었어
정말 진심으로 유감이야
Listen, I heard about the fire.
I'm real, real sorry.
- 괜찮은거야?
- 살아있어요!
- How you holding up?
- He's alive.
- 뭐?
- 빌이요!
- What?
- Bill.
시체가 4구라기에
빌도 죽었겠구나 했었는데
They said four bodies.
I thought Bill was one of 'em.
- 아니었어?
- 아니었어요, 사실
- He wasn't?
- He's fine. In fact,
아주 쌩쌩해요
he's wonderful.
- 정말 안심이겠네
- 말로 다 못해요, 어쨌든
- That must be quite a relief for you.
- You have no idea. Anyways,
내 걱정은 하지 말아요
전 괜찮으니까
no need to worry about me.
I'm great.
자기 대체 어디 있었어?
주문 받느라 정신 없었잖아
Sweetie, where you been?
I'm up to my eyeballs in tickets.
오늘따라 정말 이쁘네
You look so beautiful today.
사랑해, 가끔가다
너무 고집을 피우지만서도
I love you, even if you are
a bigot sometimes.
왜저래요?
What's with her?
빌이 살아있데
Bill's alive.
네? 난..
What? But I thought...
알아, 나도 그랬어
I know. So did I.
나왔어요!
Order up.
알았어요! 좀 기다려요!
I'm comin'. Hold your horses.
내가 웬지 조짐이 안좋다는
메세지를 남겼었는데 그걸 듣고
He got my message that something bad
might be brewing, so he figured
- 무덤에서 하루를 보냈데요
- 춥진 않았데?
- he spent the night in the graveyard.
- Doesn't it get cold out there?
아니요, 무덤 속에 있었는걸요
He was in the ground.
어쨌든 그래서 난 빌을 못 찾은거고
그 화재난 집에서 시체가 4구 였다니까
So after I couldn't find him,
then hearing about those four bodies
at that burnt-up house, you can imagine
what I was going through.
정말 내가 어땠었는지 말도 못한다니까요
- 정말 끔찍했겠네
- 정말 말로는 설명이 안돼요
That must have been
something terrible.
You don't know.
어제 온 뱀파이어는 3명이었다면서
They said there was three vampires
that come in the other night.
- 네번째 시체는 누구야 그럼?
- 뱀파이어한테 물린 사람이래요
- Who's the fourth body?
- Some fangbanger, they're saying now.
어떤 뱀파이어들은 섹스하려고
인간을 같이 데리고 다닌데요
Some vampires like to keep
a human around for sex...
아니면 피 빨려고
and blood.
콜라 갖다드릴께요
I'll get your Cokes.
- 나왔다면서요
- 그랬지, 신입이 가져갔어
- I Thought you said "order up".
- I did. New girl took 'em.
신입?
New girl?
샌드위치, 치즈버거, 웰던 스테이크
계란 후라이, 핫윙, 소세지 구이,
BLT, cheeseburger, well-done,
fried egg on white, hot wings,
smoked sausage,
참치 샌드위치
tuna melt,
그리고 치킨 스테이크까지
이건 당신꺼겠죠?
and the chicken fried steak
must be for you.
- 감사해요, 테이블 4개 남았네요
- 대단하지 않아?
- Thank you. We've got a four-top open.
- Isn't she something?
- 오빠 애인이야?
- 나한테 화난거 아는데..
- She's with you.
- I know you're pissed at me, but...
진심으로 좋아하는 여자야
I really want you to like her.
아까는 미안해요, 당신은 저 테이블에 있고
다른 직원도 점점 바빠보이길래
Sorry about that.
You looked really swamped
and the natives
were gettin' restless so...
제이슨 여동생 맞죠?
당신 얘기 많이 들었어요
You're Jason's sister, right?
It's...
I've heard so much about you.
- 누구시죠?
- 전 에이미에요
- Who are you?
- My name's Amy.
- 에이미 벌리요, 제이슨이랑 왔어요
- 나랑 왔지
- Amy Burley. I'm with Jason.
- With me.
그 아름다운 빨간 머리를 보니 알린이시군요
정말 만나서 반가워요
You must be Arlene with the beautiful
red hair. It's so nice to meet you.
테이블 번호는 어떻게 알았죠?
How'd you know
all the table numbers?
대학때 서빙한 적이 있거든요
그래서 그냥 시계방향이겠거니 했죠
I waited tables in college
so I just assumed clockwise.
테이블1, 2, 3, 4, 5 이렇게요
You know, Table 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
5번 테이블 남자들이 당신을 좋아하나봐요
팁을 아주 두둑히 남기고 갔더군요
I think the guys at Table 5 like you,
'cause they left you a really nice tip.
- 샘! 돈 자리를 채워줄 사람을 찾은 것 같아요
- 오빠도 찾은 것 같네
I think we might have found
a replacement for Dawn.
Looks like you did too.
세상에
What?
만지지 마려무나
엄마가 다 알아서 할꺼야
Don't you touch that, sweetie pie.
Mama'll take care of the laundry.
세상에나, 레티 메!
이런 면도 있었네요!
My goodness. Lettie Mae,
ain't she the spittin' image of you.
칭찬이었단다
That's a compliment.
- 타라 메, 메이블 심킨씨 기억하지?
- 교회분이요
Tara Mae, you remember
Mable Simpkins, don't you?
- From the church.
- That's right. And why don't we see
- 그렇단다, 왜 교회에 타라 모습이 보이지 않을까?
- 교회를 안가니까요
- your smiling face there no more?
- 'Cause I stopped goin'.
돌아오기에 늦지 않았단다
It's never too late to come back.
레티 메씨는 2년 전 교회를 떠났지만
우린 오늘 다시 환영해 드렸단다
Lettie Mae left us for two years
and we welcomed her back today
- 떠난 적이 없던 사람처럼
- 부름을 들었거든요
- like she had never gone.
- I heard the call.
선하신 주님께 말씀하시길
The good Lord said, "Lettie Mae,
'레티 메, 너무 오랜 시간 떠나 있었구나
너희 교회가 그대를 필요로 한단다'
"you been away too long.
Your church needs you. "
너도 와서 봤으면 좋았을텐데
모든 교인이 성령으로 충만했단다
You should have heard her testify.
The entire congregation
was filled with the spirit.
네, 그러셨겠죠
Yeah, I bet she was full of it.
- 너희 어머니는 우리 모두에게 영감을 주셨어
- 신께 영광을
- Your mama's an inspiration to us all.
- Glory to God.
화요일에 성경공부하러 오지 않겠니?
Girl, why don't you come
to Bible group on Tuesday?
멋진 청년들은 물론 수정과도 있단다
Got plenty of nice young men
and fruit punch.
종교를 갖게 됨으로써
세상의 선함을 아는거지
A little religion do you
a world of good, baby girl.
젠장, 엄마 무슨 말 하는지 알기나 해요?
Shit. Are you even listening
to what you're sayin'?
그런식으로 모두를 속일 수 있을지 몰라도
밤만 되면 나처럼 지랄맞고 절망적일껄요
You can lie to yourself and
everyone else but when you go to bed,
you are just as fucked up
and miserable as I am.
그 이상한 모자를 쓰고 교회좀 간다고
더 나은 사람이 되는건 아니라고요
And goin' to church
and wearing a crazy-ass hat
ain't gonna make you
a better person.
내면에 악마가 있어요
She got a demon in her.
우리 손녀딸도 악마가 있죠
My granddaughter had a demon in her.
모든 곳에 다 있어요
They everywhere.
그럼요, 이해해요
Sure, I understand.
괜찮아요, 끊을게요
It's no problem.
외출만 할라치면
이놈의 보모가 다 망쳐놔
Every time I get a night off,
my babysitter falls through on me.
저기
You know,
나 애들 좋아해
I like kids, Arlene.
도넛도 좋아하고
Donuts too.
그럼
Maybe,
여자 한명 데리고와
리사는 여자가 있는걸 좋아하거든
if you brought a lady friend along.
Lisa likes a female in the house.
고향에 내려온 뒤로
여자 친구는 한명도 없는데
I ain't had a lady friend
since I come home.
그거 정말 안됐다
That's some bad luck for you,
I guess.
거기서 무슨 일 있었어?
Did something happen there
거기 말이야.. 자기 갇혀 있던데
that you been...
keeping to yourself?
말할 상대가 필요하면 나한테 말해도 돼
'Cause you could talk to me,
you know, if you're wantin' to.
아니야
No, I'd...
난 그냥 여기 앉아서 당신 말 듣고 싶어
당신 목소리가 좋거든
I'd just as soon sit here
and listen at you.
I like your voice.
당신 쇄골도
And your clavicles.
목걸이가 정말 예쁘네요
I've been admiring
your necklace all day.
고마워요, 줄을 엮은거죠
제가 만들었어요
Oh, thanks, it's a lariat.
I made it.
보석을 만들었다구요?
You make jewelry?
부수입으로는 그만이거든요
원한다면 하나 만들어줄께요
It's a easy way to earn extra money.
I can make you one, if you want.
고맙지만 제 남자친구는
은을 별로 안좋아해서요
Thanks, but I don't think
my boyfriend much likes silver.
- 우리 오빠 망나니인건 알죠?
- 네?
You know my brother's
a dog, don't you?
I'm sorry?
처음에야 매력적이고 친절하지만
당신이 지겨워지면
He's all charm and smiles
in the beginning,
but the second he gets tired of you,
바로 연락 끊을거에요
he's gonna stop callin'.
당신이 알기도 전에 벌써
다른 멍청한 여자나 꼬시고 있을거라고요
Before you know it,
he's off with some other floozy.
물론 당신이 멍청하단건 아니고요
Not... Not that you are one.
어쨌든 내 말 들어요
항상 그랬거든요
But trust me, it's as regular
as the seasons.
좋은 분인것 같은데
상처받으실까봐서요
You seem like a sweet girl.
I don't want you to get hurt.
저기요
You know,
제이슨이 어떤 사람이고 어떤 사람이 될지
반도 모르시는 것 같은데
I don't think Jason's realized
even half of what he's going to be.
당신을 평가하는건 아니지만
아마 제이슨 능력을 알면 꽤나 놀라시겠네요
I wouldn't be so quick to judge. You
might be surprised at what he's capable.
- 요즘 내가 좀 못되게 굴었지
- 왜그래?
- I've been meaning to talk to you.
- What's the matter?
내가 요즘 좀 정신이 없었거든
I've just been a mess lately.
애들도 키워야지
밤낮으로 일해야지
You know, with the kids
and the double shifts
르네일도 그렇고 모두 다 말이야
정말 너무 힘들었어
and Rene and everything,
it's been awful hard.
못되게 굴려고 그랬던건
아니라고 말해주고 싶어서
And I've probably said
some things that I don't mean,
걱정되서 그랬던거야
but that's the pressure talking.
자기를 내 여동생처럼 사랑하거든
I love you like my own sister.
알고 있지?
And you know that, right?
고맙게 생각해, 고마워
I appreciate that. Thank you.
그리고 알았어
오늘 애들 봐줄께
And sure, I'll babysit
your kids tonight.
- 난.. 그런 뜻이..
- 테리랑 말하는거 다 들었어
- I... I didn't... I mean...
- I heard you talkin' to Terry.
내가 더 낫잖아
I'm a better choice.
8시에 데리고 갈께
We'll drop 'em off at 8.
르네가 러스톤에 가자거든
오크 릿지 보이즈 공연보러 가쟤
Rene's taking me to Ruston
to see that Oak Ridge Boys tribute band.
재밌겠다
Ooh. Fun.
오늘 정말 이쁘다 타라
그 색깔 정말 잘 어울려
You look mighty pretty tonight, Tara.
That's a nice color on you.
꺼져
Fuck you.
미안해
I'm sorry, w...
성희롱이었나?
Was that sexist?
타라, 할 말이 있는데
May I have a word with you?
사무실에서 보자
In my office.
알았어요, 여기서 일하지 말라구요
사람들을 짜증나게 하죠
Hey, I get it. You said yourself
hirin' me might not work out.
I piss people off.
해고하고싶으면 해고해요
다 이해하니까
If you wanna fire me, fire me.
I totally understand.
여기서 제대로 된건
당신이랑 나뿐이야
You and I
are the only ones who get it.
엉망인 사람들은 다른 사람들이지
It's everybody else
who's fuckin' themselves up.
지겹지 않아요?
수백년 동안 계속 했을거 아니에요
I mean, you've been doin' it
for over a hundred years.
새롭지 않지 않아요?
Doesn't it get predictable?
당신이랑은 아니에요
Not with you, it doesn't.
당신은 정말 달라요
You're entirely different.
아름답고 비극적이고..
And the beauty
and the tragedy of it is...
당신이 얼마나 다른 사람인지
모르는데에 대한..
Is that you don't know
just how different you are.
내가 뭐 잘못하면 말해줘요
Please tell me
if I'm doin' something wrong.
사랑을 나누는 것만큼
더 자연스러운건 없어요
There's nothing more natural
than the act of makin' love.
내가 변하면 자연스럽지 않을거에요
Who am I to try to change
what comes naturally to you?
그래도 변화시킬 수 있다면..
But if you could change something...
하나도 변하지 않을거에요
I wouldn't change a thing.
땅 속에서 자는건 어때요?
What's it like
to sleep in the ground?
편하진 않아요
It's not exactly comfortable.
안전하긴하죠
But it is safe.
음성 메일을 3개나 듣고서야
안전해졌지만요
Which, if I recall, is what the three
voice mails required of me that night.
젠장
Oh, crap.
깜빡했는데 알린 애들을 봐주기로 했어요
Arlene. I forgot, I told her
I'd babysit the kids.
나 이만 갈까요?
Shall I go?
있어요, 알린한테도 그게 좋을거에요
Stay. It'll be good for her.
그래도 바지는 입어줘요
You can put some pants on, though.
무슨 일있어?
왜 이제야 나와?
What's wrong?
What took you so long?
뒤뜰에 있었거든
I was out back in the yard.
- 이 밤에?
- 고양이때문에요
- In your nightie?
- The cat got out.
- 다람쥐를 쫓아가더라고요
- 엄마, 뱀파이어 아저씨야
- Made friends with a squirrel.
- Mommy, look, it's a vampire.
- 자기 나한테 말 없었잖아
- 꼭 말해야하나
You didn't mention
that you had company.
I didn't think I had to.
누가 우리 애들을 봐주는지는 알아야지
Well, I got a right to know
who's looking after my children.
우리가 돌볼께
Here we are.
문제 있어?
Is there a problem?
진정해
Take it easy, ch?e.
컴튼씨도 아이들 키워보셨을거야
그렇죠?
Mr. Compton's raised a couple of them
little ones himself maybe, yeah?
맞아요
That's quite right.
이거 꼭 갖고 있으렴
알겠지?
Keep these on you,
you hear?
또
And...
- 수키 이모 옆에 꼭 붙어 있으렴
- 괜찮을꺼야, 정말
stay close to your Aunt Sookie.
They'll be fine, I promise.
- 피자 먹을사람?
- 저요!
- Who wants pizza?
- Me.
잘됐다, 마침 지금 피자가 있거든
Good, 'cause that's what
we're havin'.
- 피자도 드세요?
- 안타깝지만 못먹어요
You can eat pizza?
Well, unfortunately, no,
그래도 맛있다는건 알죠
but I understand it's delicious.
사람들이 모르는 섹스의
좋은 점이 뭐게요?
You know what's good about sex
that people never mention?
어느 곳에서나
5분에서 한시간이면 된다
For anywhere
between five minutes to an hour,
그 순간만큼은 짜증나는
인생을 잊는거죠
you forget your own fucked-up life.
좋기만 하다면야
Only if it's good.
별로면 얼마나 끔찍한
인생인지 더 생각날껄
If it's not, it reminds you
just how bad your life really is.
그렇담 당신 정말 잘하는데요
Then I guess you're pretty good.
고마워, 당신도 나쁘지 않아
Thanks, you're not bad yourself.
칭찬이 뭐 그래요
Easy on the praise, honey.
왜?
What?
- 당신도 잘한다니까
- 하지만?
- No, you're good.
- But?
아니야, 정말 잘해
당신 잘해
Nothing.
It's good. You're good.
- 내가 뭐 잘못했어요?
- 아니야
- What am I doin' wrong?
- Nothin'.
정말 별거 아니야
진짜 중요한 일 아니야
I... See... It's so minor,
it doesn't even matter.
뭔데요?
What is it?
- 그러지마
- 당장 말해요!
- Don't do this to me.
- Spit it out.
가끔가다..
Sometimes...
꿀꿀거려
you grunt.
뭐라고요?
- I what?
자.. 자연스러운거야, 이상할거 없지
그냥 소리만 그런거야
It's... It's natural. Nothing to get
worked up over. It's just a sound.
꿀꿀거리는 소리?
농장에 있는 동물처럼요?
A gruntin' sound?
Like a farm animal?
아니..운동선수 같아
No, it's... It's... It's athletic.
테니스 선수가 서브할 때 같은
Like tennis players when they serve.
세레나같다고요?
You mean like Serena?
뭐요, 내가 흑인이라
세레나 윌리엄스같은 소릴 낸다고요
What, because I'm black,
I sound like Serena Williams?
- 그런 말이 아니잖아
- 이 망할 인종차별주의자같으니
- That's not what I said.
- You racist son of a bitch.
어떻게 내가 인종차별주의자야?
당신이랑 섹스까지 했는데!
How can I be racist?
I just had sex with you.
병신같은놈
You asshole.
내 인생 최고의 10분을 만들어 놓더니
그런식으로 바로 뭉개버려?
Why'd you have to go and take
the only good 10 minutes
of my entire day
and ruin it like that?
- 10분은 더 됐잖아
- 아 꺼져! 다들 집어치워!
- I think it was more than 10 minutes.
- Oh, fuck you. Fuck you all.
- 다들?
- 전부다! 전부 꺼져!
- All who?
- Everybody. Fuck everybody!
휘핑 크림 납시오
Whipped cream.
- 저요
- 저도요
- Yeah.
- Me too.
엄마 오시기 전에
다 먹어야 할텐데
I hope you can finish this
before your mother comes back.
문제 없어요
한번은 마요네즈 한 통을 다 먹었거든요
No problem. I ate a whole jar
of mayonnaise once.
전 보고만 있었죠
I had to watch.
왜 아이스크림 못먹어요?
How come you can't have ice cream?
젖당분해효소가 부족해서 말이다
You might say
that I'm lactose intolerant.
우리 펀 이모도 그래요
Just like my Aunt Fern.
이모는 멕시코 음식도 못먹어요
Except she don't tolerate Mexicans.
수키 이모, 빌 아저씨가
이모 남자친구에요?
Aunt Sookie, is Bill your boyfriend?
빌, 당신이 제 남자친구인가요?
Bill, would you say that you're
my boyfriend?
글쎄, 코비와 리사가
허락만 해준다면야
Well, I suppose I'd have to ask
permission from Coby and Lisa.
아저씨가 수키 이모
남자친구여도 괜찮겠니?
Would it be all right if I was
Aunt Sookie's boyfriend?
꽃 사준적 있어요?
Do you buy her flowers?
왜? 아직 그런 적 없는데
Why, no, I haven't yet.
사주는게 좋을껄요
르네 아저씨는 엄마한테 항상 꽃 사줘요
You better. Rene buys flowers
for Mama all the time.
그럼 아저씨도 그래야겠구나
Then I will have to mend my ways.
그러세요, 그리고 나서 말하도록 하죠
You do that. Then we'll talk.
- 송곳니 보여주시면 안돼요?
- 그건 안될 것 같구나
Can we see your fangs?
I don't think
that's gonna be possible.
보여주마
Why, certainly.
타이어 펑크났나봐
I think we got a flat tire.
빨리좀해
애들이 기다리잖아
Come on, baby,
the kids are waitin' on us.
웬만하면 그 뱀파이어랑
오래 두고 싶지 않단말이야
I don't wanna leave them with
that vampire longer than I have to.
알았어 알았어, 빨리 하겠습니다요
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'm gettin' to it, woman.
자기
Baby.
왜?
What?
손전등좀 줘
Pass me that Maglite, will you?
젠장, 고장났나봐
Crap, it's burnt out.
확실해?
Are you sure?
확인해봐
You better check it.
건전지 간지 얼마 안됐어
I just put some fresh batteries
in there.
알린 파우어
Arlene Fowler...
제게 당신을 아내로 맞이할
영광을 주시겠습니까?
would you do me the honor
of bein' my wife?
레드 랍스타에 있을 때
왜 아무 말도 안했어?
Why didn't you say anything
at the Red Lobster?
이런건 4번이나 받아봤지만
받아도 받아도 새롭다니까
I know I've done it
four other times,
but it never gets old.
정말 너무 잘됐다
Oh, I'm so thrilled for you two.
이번에도 들러리 해줄꺼지?
Would you be a bridesmaid
for me again?
물론이지, 물어볼 필요도 없어
Why, of course.
You hardly have to ask.
정말 사랑해
Oh, honey, I love you so much.
당신들도 머지 않았죠?
Maybe you two are next, huh?
그니까 법적으로도 허용되면 말이에요
Well, I mean, when it becomes legal.
엄마, 왜그래?
Mommy, what's going on?
아가
Sweetie,
엄마 결혼식에서 꽃을 들어주렴!
you're gonna be my flower girl.
좋은 아침
Morning, dear.
이거 다 만든거에요?
Did you make all this?
당신 할머님 요리법좀 따라해봤어요
I borrowed some of
your grandmother's old recipes.
그래도 다 내가 직접 한거에요
But the handiwork is all mine.
뭐부터 먹어야할지 모르겠네요
I don't even know where to begin.
여기 비스켓부터 먹어봐요
방금 구운거에요
Well, I would start with the biscuits.
They just came out of the oven.
오늘 날씨 맑을거래요
Gonna be clear skies all day.
잠깐만요, 빌 지금 해 떴잖아요
Wait, Bill, it's light out.
그렇네요
I suppose it is.
아니 아니, 내가 전화할께
No. No, I'll make the call.
어머님은 몇 년 전에 돌아가셨지만
켄터키에 다른 가족이 있어
His mama passed a couple years back,
but he had some
family in Kentucky.
치과의사가 좀 전에 확인해줬어
가장 먼저 알려줘야 할 것 같아서
His dentist confirmed the match
just a bit ago.
I thought you should be
the first to know.
젠장
Goddammit.
왜 닐이야?
Why Neil?
정말 조용한 아이였는데
He was such a quiet kid.
그런 놈들이랑 어울려 놀줄 몰랐어
I'd have never thought
he'd get mixed up with fangers.
젠장
Damn.
신원을 확인할 거라곤
이빨밖에 남지 않았다니
To have nothing left of you
to ID but teeth.
몬로에 있는 장례식장에 맡길까?
You wanna maybe let one of
the homes in Monroe handle him?
내 밑에서 일하던 친구야
내가 해야지
He worked for me. I owe it to him.
몇 시간만 기다려줘
내가 거두러 갈께
Give me a couple hours,
I'll come over and claim him, okay?
알았네, 고마워 마이크
Okay. Thanks, Mike.
엄청 울지?
Pretty tore up?
모르고 있었나봐
Blind-sided him.
뱀파이어 노리개였다고는
전혀 모르고 있더라고
Had no idea Neil was a fangbanger.
말도 안돼, 걔 좀 으스스했다고
Jesus, Bud, the kid was creepy.
어떤 19살 짜리가 장례식장에서
일을 하냐고
What 19 year-old goes to work
for a funeral home?
난 15살때 도살장에서 일했는데
I worked in a slaughterhouse
when I was 15.
아주 신선한 곱창도 줬어
They made me clean chitlins.
괴짜가 납셨군
Speaking of freaks...
그게 다에요
And that's it.
바를 떠나고 뭘 하는지
내가 어떻게 알겠어요
I got no control over what people do
after they leave the bar.
그 뱀파이어들때문에 눈에 띄게
화를 낸다거나 한 사람은 없나?
You remember anyone
being unusually angry
over what those vampires
did to your bar?
모두 다요
모두 다 화가 났죠
Everyone.
We were all angry.
그냥 마을 사람 전체를
다 심문하고 다니지 그래요?
Heck, you might as well
interrogate the whole town.
우리끼리 말이지만
Between you and me,
당신들이 범인 못찾아도
난 별로 상관도 없다고요
I wouldn't be heartbroken
if you didn't find who did it.
알아 듣겠어요?
You know what I'm sayin'?
스택하우스 부인 일은
정말 비극이지만
Old Mrs. Stackhouse, on the other hand,
now that's a real tragedy.
그 부인과 돈, 모뎃 피킨스
모두 말이에요
Her and Dawn and Maudette Pickens,
one right after the other.
뭐 단서라도 있나요?
You fellas got any leads on that?
지금 조사 중일세
We're workin' on some right now.
잘됐네요, 응원할께요
Good. I'm pullin' for you guys.
뭐 다른게 기억나거든
햄버거 먹으러 올 때 말해주게나
You remember anything else,
we'll be havin' a burger inside.
가지, 앤디
Come on, Andy.
한가지만 더
One other thing.
최근 숲에서 시간을 보낸 적이 있나?
You recall spendin' any time
out in the woods lately?
그랬죠
Some.
알고 있었잖아요
But you knew that already,
didn't you?
만약
If...
내가 말해주면
If I tell you,
비밀 지켜요
You have to keep this a secret.
마을 사람 누구도 알면 안돼요
All right, nobody in town knows.
저희 가족이 자연주의거든요
But, I come from
a family of naturists.
새 관찰하는거?
Like bird watchers?
아니요, 그런 자연주의 말고
다른 자연주의요
No. No, not naturalists.
Naturists.
자연주의자들은
Naturists believe in
자유인이거든요
a freer
옷 입는건 선택이다 뭐 이런식이죠
clothing-optional kind of lifestyle.
당신 나체주의자야?
You're a nudist?
아뇨, 세상에 절대 아니죠
No. Good Lord, no.
저희 부모님이 그랬죠
But my folks were,
말하긴 부끄럽지만
I'm embarrassed to say.
거의 나체주의자 도시에서
시간을 많이 보내시곤 하셨어요
They spent most of their lives
at a nudist colony.
그래? 여기 근처야?
Oh, yeah? Around here?
아뇨, 텍사스에 있어요
보몬트 근처에 있죠
No, in Texas, just outside Beaumont.
근데
But,
부모님이 돌아가신 이후로
ever since they passed,
그걸 기리고자 제가
일년에 한번씩..
I honor their memory
once a year by...
부모님이 그랬던 것처럼
숲을 뛰어다니곤 하거든요
taking a run through the woods
the way they used to. It's...
저만의 애도 방식이랄까요
It's my private way of mourning.
누가 그걸 봤다니 미안할 뿐이죠
I'm sorry if anybody had to see it.
뭐
What?
누나 제대로 당했네
Hooker, you done got took.
그거 엑소시즘 아니야
완전 사기당했네
That was no damn exorcism,
that was a straight-up con job.
근데 뭐가 더 짜증나는줄 알아?
You know what
the fucked-up thing is?
- 뭔데
- 효과가 있었어
- What?
- It worked.
무슨 외계인이 광선을 쏴서
엄마 뇌를 바꿔놓은 것 같다고
It was like aliens beamed down
and switched out her brain.
그럼 445달러짜리 광선이네
Then that was 445 well-spent.
이런, 행복해 하라고
Shit. Happy dance.
그럼 없앤 것만으로도 기뻐해야지
그..
You should be glad
to be rid of that...
- 누나네 엄마니까 그만 말할께
- 꺼져
- That's your mom. I ain't gonna say it.
- Fuck that.
평생동안 해온 일이 그 후두교 여자가
돌 좀 올려놨다고 사라진다는게 말이돼?
All the shit you've built up
doesn't go away because a hoodoo woman
moves some rocks around on your belly.
효과 있었다며
I thought you said it worked.
사기당한거라며
I thought you said it was a con job.
돈 쓴 가치가 있었으면
사기는 아니지
Heifer, it's not a con job
if you got your money's worth.
젠장
Hell.
누가 알겠어
And who knows?
누나한테도 효과 있을지
It might do you some good too.
난 그 말도 안되는 거에
445달러 쓸 생각 전혀 없다
I don't have another 445
to waste on bullshit.
누나가 이해를 못해서 그러는거야
You just saying that
'cause you don't understand it.
내말 들어
And trust me,
이 세계는 우리가 이해 못할
것들로 가득차 있어
this world is filled with things
we will never understand.
우울증약을 달고 사는거랑 비교하면
445달러면 싼거지
Compared to a lifetime
of Zoloft, 445's a bargain.
- 뭐해?
- 비타민 먹어요
- Hey, what you doing?
- Vitamin.
전에는 비타민 먹은 적 없잖아
I've never seen you
take a vitamin before.
근데요?
So what?
내가 데오드란트 바르거나
머리 감는거
You've never seen me
put on deodorant or wash my hair
고양이 먹이주는거 본 적 있어요?
그것도 항상 하는건데
or feed my cat, have you?
But I do all those things.
당신 허락을 받아야 하는건가요?
I don't need a permission slip
from you.
미치겠군
Christ.
괜찮았어?
Good day?
V가 필요해
I need V.
뭐?
What?
당분간은 필요 없을거라며
I thought you said
you didn't need any again until...
- 다시 필요할 때까진
- 다시 필요해
- you needed it again.
- Well, I need it.
내 눈을 봐
Look me in the eye.
당신은 필요 없다고 말해봐
Tell me that you don't want it too.
물론 나도 필요해
Yeah, of course I do,
근데 라파옛은 나한텐 안판다고
but Lafayette won't sell it to me.
문자 3번이나 보냈는데
I texted you three times.
- 왜 답장 안보내?
- 숫자 키를 치는게 싫어서
- Why didn't you reply?
- I hate using the number keys to type.
뭐 듣는거야?
What are you listenin' to?
젊었던 시절에 들었던거지
From my younger days.
중세 스웨덴 말만 안다면
정말 아름다운 곡이지
It's really quite beautiful
if you know Old Swedish.
부탁이 있어
I have a favor to ask of you.
부탁이야, 명령이야?
A favor or an order?
네가 받아들이기에 따라 다르지
Depends on how you look at it.
솔직히
Honestly,
수키를 너 혼자만
가질 수 있다고 생각해?
did you think
you could keep her to yourself?
스토킹하는 것 같아
It feels a little like stalking,
don't it?
세상에서 가장 자연스러운 일이야
It's the most natural thing
in the world.
사냥이지
The hunt.
복제 소고기랑 인스턴트 식품에 빠지기 전엔
늘상 하던 일이었다고
People used to do this before
we got complacent with cloned beef
and prepackaged dinners.
헤드라이트 꺼
Headlights off.
전에도 해봤어?
You done this before?
5미터 뒤에 있어
패리쉬 로드부턴 10미터
Stay five lengths behind,
10 if we get on the Parish Road.
그동안 안녕하셨나
Well, hey there, sweetness.
파티 준비 되셨나?
You ready to party?
알겠다는 말이로군
I'll take that as a yes.
천박하긴
Nasty.
당신을 위해 특별히 준비했어
I bought this specially for you.
당신 말이 생각났거든
I remember you said
멜롯을 좋아한다는 말
you go for merlot.
멜로츠에서 일한다고 했지
I said I worked at Merlotte's.
뭐 어쨌든간
한 번 따라줘봐
But whatever.
Pour me some anyhow.
좋아, 잠깐만
에디 쥬스먼저 주셔야지
All right, baby.
Eddie juice first.
그리고 노는거야
Then we play.
그렇지
Oh, there it is.
항상 월요일이 기다려져
I always look forward
to Monday nights.
히어로즈랑
First Heroes, then...
그리고 당신
you.
하루종일 TV만 보면
뱀파이어로써 재미를 못보잖아
What fun is it being a vampire
if all you do is watch TV?
난 TV가 좋으니까
Well, I like TV.
내 말은 바에 가보란 말이야
I'm just sayin'
you should try the bars.
섹스하는거 좋아하잖아
I know you like getting laid too.
바에 갈 일이 뭐가 있어
Why should I go to the bars?
오늘이 있는데
I got this.
당신도 나 좋아하지?
You like me, don't you, Lafayette?
물론이지
Sure, I like you.
내 말은
I mean...
내가 피를 주지 않아도
날 원할거잖아 그렇지?
even if I wasn't helping out
with the blood, you'd still
want me, right?
그런건 왜 물어봐?
Why you even got to ask me that?
당신이 그냥 사업적인 일로
찾아온다고 생각하는게 싫어서 그래
I'd hate to think
it's just business for you
when you come over.
물론 아니지
Of course not.
혹시 내가 다른 놈들하고도
놀아날까봐 그런거야?
What, you think I fool around
with all my business associates?
다됐군
Ah, there we go.
이제 당신이 얼마나 야한
늙은 뱀파이어인지 볼까나
Now show me what
a dirty old vampire you is.
너무나 원해
I want you so bad...
아플정도로
I ache.
이리와 자기
Well, come on, baby.
내가 돌봐줄께
I'll take care of you.
오늘 데이트 하자면서요
You said you wanted
to go out tonight.
팡타지아에 오잔 말은 아니었어요
I did not mean Fangtasia.
여기 오는 사람들 모두 한심하게
뱀파이어랑 섹스나 하려고 가는거잖아요
I mean, really,
all those pathetic people
who come here looking
for sex with vampires.
알아요, 좀 비열하죠
I know. It's despicable.
그런 말은 아니잖아요
You know what I mean.
어쨌든, 5분? 10분?
So, what, five, 10 minutes?
에릭이 원하는 만큼 우린 있어야죠
As long as Eric requires us.
에릭이 원하는 만큼
내가 있어야 한다는 건가요
You mean as long as he requires me.
나한텐 물어보지도 않았잖아요
Didn't even have the decency
to ask me himself.
당신은 내 것이잖아요
당신 허락을 받을 필요가 없죠
You are mine. He didn't need
to ask your permission.
- 도서관 책 고르듯 나한테 그럴 순 없어요
- 안타깝지만 그럴 수 있어요
He cannot check me out
like a library book.
Unfortunately, Sookie, he can.
- 에릭은 5번 구역 보안관이에요
- 보안관이요?
- Eric is sheriff of Area 5.
- Sheriff?
우리 사이에선 엄청난
자리에 있다는걸 의미해요
It's a position of great power
among our kind.
화나게 해서 좋을 거 없어요
We do not wanna anger him.
적절한 이유가 있는 부탁이라면
들어줘야 한다고요
As long as the requests are reasonable,
we should accede to his wishes.
오늘 정말 끔찍한 꿈을 꿨어요
I had this crazy dream this morning.
같이 앉아서 아침을 먹는데
We were sitting, eating breakfast,
갑자기 햇빛이 들어와
당신이 타버렸어요
and all of a sudden
the sunlight set you on fire.
그런 식으로는 아니에요
It wouldn't happen quite that way.
햇빛이 날 약하게 만들고
The sunlight would
severely weaken me
결국엔 물론 죽을 수도 있지만
and eventually, of course,
I would die.
화염에 타 죽지는 않아요
But I wouldn't burst into flames.
적어도 그렇게 확 죽진 않아요
Not right away, at least.
그렇다면
So I guess
같이 아침 먹을 일은 없겠네요
we'll never have breakfast together.
올 줄 알았어
I knew you'd come.
들어가지
Let's go inside.
아니 확실해
No, I'm quite certain.
여기 기록도 있는걸
We keep extensive records here.
1958년 기록이지
All the way back to 1958.
멜롯이라는 이름은 여기에 없어
Never had anybody
by the name of Merlotte here.
그럼 그 지역에선 나체주의자는
자네 뿐이라는거지?
And you're sure you're the only
nudist colony in the area?
자연주의 공동체지
Naturist community.
제퍼슨 주에선 여기가
최초의 최고의 유일한 성역인게지
We're the first, finest and only
clothing-optional sanctuary
in all of Jefferson County.
알았네
All right.
- 고맙네
- 한번 들려, 응?
- Thanks very much.
- You come visit us, you hear?
매 달 바베큐 파티를 하거든
Got a barbecue every month.
팸, 롱섀도우, 그리고 난
이 클럽의 동업자다
Pam, Longshadow and I
are partners in this club.
최근 장부를 보니
6만 달러가 비어 있더군
And we recently noticed that $60,000
has gone missing from our books.
브루스가..
And Bruce...
우리 회계사고 말이야
is our accountant.
- 이 사람 마음 속부터 들어봐
- 아무 말도 안하는데요
- Perhaps you can listen to him.
- He's not saying anything.
부끄러워하지마
Don't be coy.
인간의 도움을 받는 것만큼
더 부끄러운 것도 없으니까
It's humbling enough to turn
to a human for assistance.
- 네 능력을 잘 알고 있어
- 저도 당신 능력을 알죠
- We know what you can do.
- And I know what you can do too.
최면 걸어보는게 어때요?
Why don't you just glamour him?
널 부르기 전에 다 해봤던 거야
Now, don't you think we tried everything
before summoning you?
그러니
So...
당신이 도와준다면 정말
나에게나 캠튼씨에게나 기쁨이겠는데
it would be a great favor to me
and to Mr. Compton if you help us.
내가 알아내면요, 그 다음엔요?
If I find out who did it, then what?
경찰에 넘겨 그 쪽에서 해결하게 할꺼야
We'll turn that person over to police
and let the authorities handle it.
수백년을 살고도 거짓말 하나
제대로 못하네요
Hundreds of years old
and you're still a terrible liar.
Come on.
협상해요
I'll make you a deal.
범인을 경찰에 넘긴다고 약속하면
필요할 때 도와드리죠
If you promise to hand over
the person who did this to the police,
I'll agree to help you
any time you want.
좋아
All right.
안될거 없지
Why not?
젠장, 이 미친년은 뭘 하려는거야?
대체 난 왜 뱀파이어 밑에서 일하겠다고 했지
Shit, what's this crazy bitch doing?
Why did I agree to work for vampires?
젠장, 좋은 생각이 아니었는데
난 이 병신들한테 솔직했다고
Goddamn it, I knew it was a bad idea.
I've been straight with these fuckers.
얘네 돈을 훔치다니 병신이군
돈이 빈다고 말한건 난데 말이야
Gotta be an idiot
to steal from them.
Jesus Christ, I was the one
who reported it.
브루스, 괜찮아요
숨을 들이쉬어 봐요
Bruce, it's okay.
Take a deep breath.
돈을 훔쳤나요?
Did you steal their money?
아니요, 믿어주세요
정말 아니에요, 맹세코..
No, no. You gotta believe me.
I didn't do it. I swear to...
누가 그랬는지 아나요?
Do you know who did?
나도 알면 불기라도 하지
대체 누구야
No, I wish. I would turn
that fucker in. Who was it?
진저는 완전 또라이니 못할거고
섹시하긴 하지, 한번 자보고 싶다
Couldn't have been Ginger.
She's too dumb.
Although she's hot as shit.
I'd fuck her if I could.
사실이에요
He's tellin' the truth.
정말 저 말라깽이가
뚱땡이 편 드는거 믿어?
You trust the skinny human
to clear the fat one?
다음 사람 데리고와
Bring the next one in.
현금 있어?
살꺼야?
You got cash?
Are you buying?
내가 한 말이나 잘 하면 돼
나머진 내가 알아서 할께
Just remember your lines, that's all I
need from you. I'll handle the rest.
- 저 남자랑 섹스시킬건 아니지?
- 내가 알아서 한다고 했잖아
I'm not gonna
have to have sex with him?
I said that I will handle it.
나 별로 안똑똑하다고 생각하는건 알겠는데
저 뱀파이어가 우리 둘 다 죽일 수도 있다고
I know you probably don't think
I'm all that smart,
but I do know that that vampire
can kill us both
문에 들어서기도 전에 말이야
before we even get in the door.
알아서해
You'll handle it.
그건 대체 뭐야?
What is that?
뱀파이어 권리 범안을 통과시키려
좌파에서 노력하는 동안에
While the wing nuts on the left
keep pushing their so-called
vampire-rights legislation,
전 기본적인 인권에 대해 고민했습니다
I'm more concerned
with basic human rights.
우리 아이들이 피에 굶주린 야만인들의
위협 없이 등교할 수 있도록 말입니다
The right for our sons and daughters
to go to school without fear
of molestation
by a bloodthirsty predator
in the playground
교실에서의 안전도요
or in the classroom.
누군가는 뱀파이어들로 부터
공공의 안전을 지키기 위해 일어설 때입니다
Someone has got to take a stand
for public safety
over permissiveness and immorality.
제 생각엔 너무 격한 것 같군요
If you ask me, he's protesting
a little too hard.
우물 밖으로 좀 나오세요
스티브 목사님
Come out of the closet,
Reverend Steve.
제 뱀파이어 친구들이
당신을 물고 싶어하네요
I know plenty of friendly vampires
who'd like to take a bite out of you.
스티브 뉼린의 선동적 연설은
정말 인간인 저조차도 부끄럽군요
Oh, but truly, it's inflammatory talk
from folks like Steve Newlin
who make me ashamed
to call myself a human.
시청해주셔서 감사합니다
Thanks for watching.
잠시 후에 뵙죠
We'll be bite back.
누구시죠?
Who is it?
라파옛 레이놀즈의 친구인데요
라파옛이 가보라고 해서요
I'm a friend of Lafayette Reynolds.
He sent me for you.
세상에
Jesus Christ.
- 다리 묶어
- 진심이야?
- Get his feet.
- Are you kidding?
- 다리 묶으라고!
- 알았어 알았어
- Get his feet!
- Okay, okay.
안돼요! 제발요
원하는건 다 드릴께요
No, please! I'll give you
anything you want.
- 닥쳐!
- 에이미, 대체 뭐하는거야
- Shut up!
- Amy, what the hell?
- 이름 부르지마, 멍청아
- 피 조금 뽑아서 가는줄 알았어
No names, dumb ass.
I thought we'd take
a little blood and go.
- 입좀 닥치라고!
- 이럴수가
- Shut the fuck up.
- Jeez.
- 빨리 들어!
- 뭐?
- Now, come on, lift.
- What?
좀 들라고!
Lift him up.
안돼요!
Please! No!
원하는건 뭐든 드릴께요 제발요!
No! I'll do anything
you want. Please.
마지막 인간이야
This is the last of our humans.
섹시한데
Yummy.
여기 이 여성분이 질문을 할거야
This woman has some
questions for you.
친절하게 대답해줘
Be a good girl
and answer them, will you?
그러죠, 주인님
Aye, aye, master.
만지지마
Don't you touch me.
잡고 있어
Hold her still.
진저, 누군가 여기 돈을 훔쳤어요
Ginger, someone's been
stealing money from the bar.
그래?
Really?
뭘 쳐다봐 미친년아
난 아무짓도 안했어
Don't look at me.
I didn't do nothing.
내가 했다고 말하면 죽여버릴줄 알아
I'll beat the shit out of you
if you say I did.
훔친건 내가 아니라고
It wasn't me that took it.
진저는 아니에요
She didn't do it...
- 하지만 범인을 알고 있어요
- 뭐?
- but she knows who did.
- What?
무슨 소릴
Fuck you.
젠장 어떻게 안거야?
아무한테도 말 안했는데
Shit. How'd she know?
I didn't tell anyone, I swear.
젠장, 날 죽일지도 몰라
Fuck, he's gonna kill me.
누구요? 누가 죽여요?
Who? Who's gonna kill you?
진저, 이름이 뭐에요?
Ginger, honey, what's his name?
아무 소리가 안나요
기억이 지워진 것 처럼
It's blank,
like her memory's been erased.
맹세코 아무것도 몰라요
I don't know anything, I swear.
- 최면에 걸렸었네
- 뱀파이어 짓이었어요
- She's been glamoured.
- It's a vampire.